guava.com 2016-05-25

# Privacy Policy - NetBooster - Your Digital Performance Architects

**Welcome to NetBooster S.A.**

Thank you for your interest in our website and our company. We take the privacy of our users and their personal information very seriously.

 **Legal Information**

 **Web Editor** **|** This Website is published by:

NETBOOSTER S.A.  
Head office: 4-6 passage Louis Philippe 75011 Paris - FRANCE  
Social capital: 1.542.920,70€  
Registered in the Paris Corporate Register under number B 418 267 704  
SIREN 418 267 704

Phone: 01 40 40 27 00  
E-mail:  [info-group@netbooster.com ** **](mailto:info-group@netbooster.com "Group Contact Email ")

 **Legal representative and publishing director:  
** Mr. Tim Ringel

 **Person in charge of the Website and content:  
** Secrétaire Générale Groupe - Miss Natalie Dusey

 **Hosting** **| this Website is hosted by:**

OVH SAS  
Social capital: 10.000.000 €  
Head office: 2 rue Kellermann - 59100 Roubaix - FRANCE  
Registered in the Lille Metropole Corporate Register under number B 424 761 419  
APE code: 6202A  
VAT number: FR 22 424 761 419

Tel number: +35 316 390 037 

 **Privacy Protection**

This website is operated by NetBooster S.A. This policy (together with our Terms & Conditions and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

By using and visiting this website “www.netbooster.com” (hereafter the “Website”) and or by submitting your personal information to us, and or by registering as a user of the services that we provide, you agree to us using your personal information as set out in this privacy policy.  

Any dispute which may arise over privacy will be subject to this policy, the data protection notice (if any) incorporated into this Website and the provisions of French laws. We may change our privacy policy from time to time. We therefore ask you to check it occasionally to ensure that you are aware of the most recent version that will apply each time you access this site.

We attach great importance to the protection of your data and safeguarding your privacy. To ensure that you are fully informed about the collection and use of personal data on our website, please note the following information.

Our Website may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

 **1. Anonymous data collection or other form when registration is required**

You can visit our Website without telling us who you are. We do not save the name of your Internet service provider, or the website from which you visit us, or the name of the requested file.

 **2. Collection and processing of personal data**

 **2.1.**  While navigating through certain pages of this Website, internet users may communicate personal information to NetBooster S.A (hereinafter “NetBooster” or “we” or “us”). Communicating such information or data is optional. Any personal data collected in that manner is intended exclusively for NetBooster S.A, its subsidiaries or the members of its sales network, for the purposes of surveys, analyses or studies and, in the case of forms pertaining to recruitment, for the purpose of communicating and processing job offers from NetBooster Group & subsidiary companies (hereinafter the "NetBooster Group").

Please note that the transmission of the data is not encrypted and therefore no confidential information should be sent via the contact form.

Except for the uses mentioned above, such information is considered confidential and treated as such.

 **2.2. Your Rights**

Pursuant to the French law entitled “Informatique et Libertés” ["Information Technology and Civil Liberties"] No. 78-17 of 6 January 1978, as amended by subsequent laws, you have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data.

From a general perspective, pursuant to the same law you have a right to access and, if necessary, modify, correct or delete any personal data about you. You are also entitled to oppose the processing of your personal data, for legitimate reasons. In the event your request to remove or to oppose the processing of your personal data prevents us from providing you information or services, we shall bear no liability in this respect.

 **2.3. Implementation of your rights**

You can exercise your rights in accordance with the aforementioned law at any time by contacting us at info-france[at]netbooster.com or at the following address: NetBooster Website Query, NetBooster S.A., 4-6 passage Louis Philippe 75011 Paris – FRANCE. You must enclose a copy of your identity card bearing your signature. Your request must specify the returning mailing address. NetBooster S.A. shall have a period of 2 (two) months after receipt of the request to communicate, supplement or delete the information, as the case may be.

Any request to be provided with a copy of personal data we hold about you may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs.

Internet users who consent on forms to receive e-mails containing information and requests from NetBooster S.A. and NetBooster Group companies may revoke said consent at any time, either by clicking on the hyperlink provided to that purpose at the bottom of the e-mails they receive or by sending an e-mail with "désabonnement" (Unsubscribe) on the subject line to: info-france[at]netbooster.com

 **2.4.**  Pursuant to Article 6 of the Act of 21 June 2004 entitled "pour la confiance dans l'économie numérique" [“law promoting confidence in e-commerce”], the web hosting service retains the Website users' connection data covered by professional secrecy and processed in compliance with the statutory provisions on personal data when such data makes it possible to identify the users of the Website.

 **3. Where we store your personal data**

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staffs operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, for example, the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

 **  4.**  **Cookies**

Our website uses 3 types of cookies. A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we put on your computer if you agree. It is sent to your web browser and stored on your computer’s hard drive. These cookies:

    * allow us to distinguish you from other users of our Website, which helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our Website; and also allows us to improve our site; ** **
    * allow us to track your progress through the site and to understand and save your preferences for future visits; and
    * enable us measure the frequency of page views and general navigation.

You may set your web browser to notify you of cookie placement requests or to decline cookies completely.  You can delete the files that contain cookies; those files are stored on your hard drive.

You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of our Website.

Cookies come in many forms. We have set out below the 3 types and categories of cookies that are used. This section refers to all types of categories of cookies and not just those we use on our website(s).

 **4.1. First and third-party cookies:** whether a cookie is first-party or third-party refers to the domain placing the cookie. First-party cookies are those set by a website that is being visited by the user, the website displayed in the URL window e.g. [www.netbooster.com](http://www.netbooster.com/). Third-Party cookies are cookies that are set by a domain other than that of the website being visited by the user. If a user visits a website and another entity sets a cookie through that website this would be a third-party cookie.

 **4.2. Persistent cookies:** these cookies remain on a user's device for the period of time specified in the cookie. They are activated each time that the user visits the website that created that particular cookie.

 **4.3. Session cookie:** these cookies allow website operators to link the actions of a user during a browser session. A browser session starts when a user opens the browser window and finishes when they close the browser window. Session cookies are created temporarily. Once you close the browser, all session cookies are deleted.

By agreeing to the opt-in following the display of the Cookies Box at the beginning of your navigation on our website you agree to the use of such cookies. We inform you that you can refuse cookies at any time, if your browser so permits.

 **5. Storage of browsing information**

When you browse through the Website, information is stored in your computer through the "DOM Storage" process. Such information does not permit the publisher or web hosting service to identify the internet users: on the other hand, the DOM Storage process records information on how you browse our Website on your computer (the pages you have viewed, date and time of viewing, etc.) that we can read during your subsequent visits. You can delete that information manually by performing the following steps:

 ** _In the case of Microsoft Internet Explorer 9.0:_**

1\. From the "Tools" menu, select "Delete Browsing History"; select the "Cookies" checkbox and click "OK".   
2\. Click on the "Confidentiality" tab.   
3\. Use the cursor to select the desired setting.

To delete all the storage areas irrespective of the source, clear the checkbox "Store data from favorite websites".

 ** _For Firefox:_**

1\. From the "Tools" menu, "Options" and then "Privacy""   
2\. Click on "Clear my history now

 ** _For Opera 6.0:_**

1\. Choose the “File” menu > “Preferences”  
2\. Privacy

 ** _For Chrome:_**

1\. Choose "Tools" menu > "Options"  
2\. Click on "Privacy" option  
3\. Section "Cookies"

 ** _For Safari:_**

1\. Choose "Tools" menu >"Options"  
2\. Click on "Privacy" option  
3\. Section "Cookies"

 **6. Use of Facebook plug-ins**

We have incorporated into our Website the social network, facebook.com (hereinafter "Facebook") plug-ins. Facebook is a company Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA.

If you access one of our Website pages from our own Website containing this plug-in, your browser will build a direct connection to the servers of Facebook. The content of the plug-in is transferred by Facebook directly to your browser and integrated by the latter to the website.

When accessed, Facebook receives the information that someone has accessed the corresponding page of our Website. If at this moment you are logged into Facebook, Facebook can associate the visit to your Facebook account, even if you have not clicked on, for example the “Like” button. If you click on the “Like-Button”, the corresponding information is sent from your browser directly to Facebook and saved there. In addition, the information that you have visited our Website will be sent to Facebook, regardless of whether one of the plug-ins is operated or not.

Information about the purpose and extent of the data collected and the further processing and use of the data by Facebook, as well as your setting options to protect your private sphere can be found in the[  **data protection guidelines of Facebook**](http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/).

To prevent the transmission and storage of personal data about you and your surfing behaviour by Facebook, through our website, please log off Facebook before you visit our website.

 **7. Use of Google Analytics**

Our website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, California, 94043 USA, (hereinafter referred to as "Google"). Google Analytics uses so-called "cookies", text files that are stored on your computer, to help analyse how users use the site by you. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to a Google server in the US and stored there. If the IP anonymisation on this website is activated, your IP address will, however, first be shortened by Google in countries of the European Union or in other Contracting States to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases is the full IP address sent to a server of Google in the USA and shortened there. On behalf of the operator of this website Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other use of this website activity and internet related services Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.

You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however, we must point out that you may not be able to use all features of this website to the full extent. By using this website you agree to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner described above and for the purposes set out above. The data collection and storage can be revoked at any time with effect for the future. Our contact address for the contradiction can be found at the end of this document. Alternatively, you can use the opt-out add-on from [Google Analytics](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en "google analytics link"), if it is available for your browser.

Moreover you can prevent the collection of the data created by the cookie and connected to your use of the website (incl. your IP address) being sent to Google and the processing of this data through Google, if you download and install the browser plug-in available under the following link: [ **Browser add on for deactivation of Google Analytics**](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en). 

It should be noted that this website uses Google Analytics with the extension of the IP anonymisation and therefore IP addresses are processed only shortened to exclude a direct personal.

 **8. Opting out of cookies**

 **8.1. Opt-in:** By agreeing to the opt-in following the display of the Cookies Box at the start of your navigation to our Website, you agree to the use of such cookies.

 **8.2. Opt-out:**   However, if you would like to opt-out of the NetBooster cookie use and **GroundControl** cookie use, please opt-out at [this site](http://www.netbooster.com/opting-out-of-cookies/)

 **9. Use the Google "+1" button**

On our Website, we use the "+1" button of the social network Google+ (Google Plus) of Google.

With every visit to a web page of our site that has a “+1″ button, “+1″ button causes the browser used by you to load and show the optical representation of the “+1″ button of the Google server. The Google server is thus informed which particular pages of our website you are currently visiting. Google records your browser activity by showing a “+1″ button for a period of up to two weeks for the purpose of system maintenance and fixing mistakes. A more extensive assessment of your visit to a page of our website with a “+1″ button will not be made.

If you click on the “+1″ button while you are logged into Google+ (Google Plus), through your Google profile, Google will gather information about the URL’s recommended by you, your IP address and other browser-related information, so that your “+1″ recommendation is saved and can be made publicly accessible. Your “+1″ recommendation can be inserted as an indication together with your profile name and your photo in Google services, as for example in search results or in your Google profile (as “+1″ Tab in your Google profile), or an other places on websites and notices in Internet.

At the following Internet address you can find the data protection guidelines of Google on the “+1″ button with more detailed information about the collection, passing on and use of data by Google, about your associated rights and about your profile setting options: [**https://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/policies/privacy/**](https://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

 **10. Use of Twitter ("Tweet" button)**

Functions of the Twitter service are integrated on our website. These functions are offered by Twitter Inc., Twitter, Inc. 1355 Market St, Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94103, USA. Through the use of Twitter and the "Re-Tweet" the web pages you visit are linked to your Twitter account and made ​​known to other users. This data is also transmitted to Twitter.

We must point out that we provide these pages without knowledge of the content of the data provided by Twitter or its potential use. Further information on Twitter’s data protection and privacy policies can be found on [http://twitter.com/privacy](https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=en).

Your privacy settings on Twitter, you can change the account settings under[ http://twitter.com/account/settings](https://twitter.com/settings/account).

 **11. Use of StormAnalytics ™ ("DC Storm")**

This Website uses StormAnalytics ™, a web analytics service provided by DC Storm Germany GmbH ("DC Storm"). DC Storm uses so-called "Cookies", text files that are stored on your computer, to help analyse how users use the Website.

The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to a server of DC Storm and stored there. On behalf of the operator of this website DC Storm will use this information to evaluate your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other use of this website activity and internet related services. 

DC Storm will not associate your IP address with any other data held by DC Storm. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however, we must point out that you may not be able to use all features of this website in this case. 

By using this site, you agree to the processing of data about you by DC Storm in the manner described above and for the purposes set out above.

 **12. Use of XING plugins (XING Share Button):**

On this Website the "XING Share Button" is used. If you access one of our web pages from our own Website containing this button, your browser will build a direct connection to the servers of XING AG ("XING"), with which the "XING Share Button" functions (the calculation / display of the counter value in particular) are provided. 

XING does not collect personally identifiable information (Non-PII) from you when you visit our website. XING stores no particular IP addresses. There is no analysis of your usage behaviour over the use of cookies in connection with the "XING Share Button". 

We must point out that we provide these pages without knowledge of the content of the data provided by XING or its potential use. Further information on the "XING Share Button" and XING’s data protection and privacy policies can be found on <https://www.xing.com/app/share?op=data_protection>.

 **13. Use of LinkedIN plugins (Share Button)**

On our web pages, plugins of the social network, LinkedIn is integrated. LinkedIn is a company, LinkedIn Corporation of 2029 Stierlin Court, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA (hereinafter "LinkedIn"). The LinkedIn plugin you can see in the LinkedIn logo or the "Recommend" button ("Share") on the  side of our Website. If you access one of our Website pages from our own Website containing this plug-in, your browser will build a direct connection to the servers of LinkedIn. The content of the plug-in is transferred by LinkedIn directly to your browser and integrated by the latter to the website.

When you visit our pages, the plugin establishes a connection between your browser and the LinkedIn server is established. LinkedIn receives the information that you have with your IP address visited our site. If you click on the LinkedIn "Recommend" button while you are logged into your LinkedIn account, you can link the content of our pages to your LinkedIn profile. As a result, LinkedIn associate the visit of our pages to your account. 

We must point out that we provide these pages without knowledge of the content of the data provided by LinkedIn or its potential use. Further details of data collection (purpose, scope, process, use) as well as your rights and options available, refer to the privacy policies of LinkedIn. This guidance can be found on [http://www.linkedin.com/static?key=privacy_policy&trk=hb_ft_priv](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy)  ready.

 **14. The use of options**

On our website, we have integrated plugins of the social network, Pinterest. This special service is operated by Pinterest Inc., 635 High Street, Palo Alto, CA, 94301, USA. The plugin options are marked with a "Pin it" button on this page.

If you click on Pinterest "Pin it" button while you are logged into your Pinterest account, you can link the content of our pages to your Pinterest profile. This allows Pinterest associate the visit of our pages to your account. We must point out that, we, as provider of the sites has no knowledge of the content of the transmitted data provided by Pinterest or its potential use. For more information on [privacy policy options](https://about.pinterest.com/en-gb/privacy-policy-0)

 **15. Use of Vimeo**

Functions of the service Vimeo is integrated on our Website. These functions are offered by Vimeo, LLC 555 West 18th Street New York, NY 10011. For more information, please see the [privacy policy Vimeo](https://vimeo.com/privacy).

 **16. Use of ShareThis**

On our Website we use the social plugins bookmarking service ShareThis Inc. (hereafter "ShareThis"), 4009 Miranda Avenue, Suite 200, Palo Alto, CA 94304-1227, USA. These plugins allow users to set bookmarks (hereafter “bookmarks”) and to post or to share their contents in social networks (such as Twitter, Facebook or Google+). If a user elects to use any of these features and at that moment the user is logged into one or more of the appropriate service (e.g., Twitter, Facebook or Google+) online at the same time, the user’s visit can be associated. ShareThis receives from us any personal information, but leads an anonymous usage statistics about the shared content. This data is deleted there regularly. For more information on data collection, analysis and processing of your data by ShareThis Inc. and your rights related thereto, see the privacy policy of ShareThis, Inc. under [http://sharethis.com/privacy](http://www.sharethis.com/legal/privacy/#sthash.0uXFfbOr.dpbs). If you do not want your visit to our website to be associated with your user accounts in the relevant social networks and social bookmarking services, we recommend you do not use the appropriate button on ShareThis on our website or using ShareThis via the link "Do not Track" to disagree.

 **17. The use of other tracking tools**

On our website are the tracking tools  **metalyzer** , by [metapeople GmbH](http://www.metapeople.com/ "metapeople homepage ") ([http://www.metapeople.com](http://www.metapeople.com/))  and **GroundControl** by NetBooster. These tracking tools on our website, enable us collect and process data for marketing and optimisation purposes. These data can be used to create pseudonymous user profiles. Without explicit consent of the data subject, however, there is no personal identifying and no data collected and combined to form a personal profile. Our web server collects information about each visitor to our Web page (the name of the Internet service provider, the website from where he/she visited us, the websites he/she visited along with the date and duration of visit). To this end, we also use our third service providers. The data collected does not contain your name or address or your eMail and thus cannot personally identifiable to.

The data collection and storage can be revoked at any time with effect for the future.

 **Opt-out:**  If you would like to opt-out of the tracking tools  **metalyzer**  and **GroundControl** by NetBooster cookie use, please opt-out at [this site](http://www.netbooster.com/opting-out-of-cookies/).

 **18. Data Security**

Your personal data will be in the order process and encrypted using SSL over the Internet. We secure our Website and other systems through technical and organisational measures against loss, destruction, access, modification or distribution of your data by unauthorised persons. Access to your account or to certain parts of our website is only possible after entering your personal password. You are responsible for keeping this password confidential. You should not share your password with anyone and close the browser window when you have finished your communication with us, especially if you share your computer with others.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Website; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

 **19. Further information and contacts**

If you have further questions about this Policy, please contact us. Questions for the collection, processing or use of personal information, the disclosure, correction, blocking and deletion of data and revocation of consent, please contact:

NetBooster S.A.  
Alexia Cassini   
4-6 Passage Louis Philippe  
75011 Paris - FRANCE  
Tel: +33 (0) 140 402 700
